fightthenewdrug.org 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy - Fight the New Drug

##### Our Commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy outlines the treatment of information collected by Fight the New Drug on the fightthenewdrug.org website. Please understand that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online this information cannot be made 100% secure and, in some cases, that information may be intercepted, collected and used by others.

We collect two types of information (personal information and anonymous information) and we may use this information to create a third type of information, aggregate information.

  * Personal information: Direct and indirect information that identifies a particular individual, such as the individual’s name, email address, and telephone number.
  * Anonymous information: Information that does not directly or indirectly identify an individual. When you use public areas of the website, you are doing so anonymously.
  * Aggregate information: Information about groups or categories of visitors, which cannot be used to identify an individual, such as number of hits per page and traffic sources.

##### We Collect The Following Information

  * Name
  * Company/School Name
  * Address
  * Email Address
  * Phone Number
  * Gender
  * Age/Date of Birth (DOB)
  * Credit/Debit Card Information

##### How We Collect Information

Information is gathered through forms filled out when you make a donation, purchase merchandise, sign the Fighter pledge, request to “Bring Fight to Your School”, request stickers, or complete any other form on fightthenewdrug.org.

We collect aggregate information for internal and marketing use only; we do not sell or rent your personal information to any individual, organization, company, government entity, or the public.

We use the information you provide when conducting a transaction to complete that transaction only. We do not share this information with outside parties.

We use email addresses to: provide you with products and services you request present you with product and service offers share new educational material give you updates on the movement gather input from you in order to optimize programs and services (this is accomplished through surveys sent via email).

We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

This website uses Google AdWords, Facebook, Instagram, and Pinterest remarketing services to advertise on third party websites (including Google, Facebook, Instagram, and Pinterest) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. It could also mean serving a product recommendation based on items you have added to your cart or viewed in the past. This remarketing may come in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Fight the New Drug website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

##### Our Commitment to Data Security

Securing the information that you share with us online is a top priority. In order to prevent unauthorized access to your information we have implemented electronic, administrative, and physical security measures. Please be aware that, despite our best efforts, no security measures are impenetrable.

Fight the New Drug reserves the right to make changes to this policy at any time. Privacy policy changes may be due to new technologies, industry practices, regulatory requirements or for other purposes. Consent will be obtained when required by applicable law.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy, please call us at 213-792-2106 or write to us at [info@fightthenewdrug.org](mailto:info@fightthenewdrug.org).

__

Like all websites, we use cookies. By continuing on this site, you agree to our use of cookies. [More](https://fightthenewdrug.org/cookie-policy/)

The cookie settings on this website are set to "allow cookies" to give you the best browsing experience possible. If you continue to use this website without changing your cookie settings or you click "Accept" below then you are consenting to this.

Close
